





Freelancer

ABOUT ME

A software developer with 1+ year of experience designing, developing, and implementing applications.

Looking for a freelance job that will help me contribute to its development while concurrently helping me develop experience and hands-on technical expertise.

I'm open to work remotely as part-time position with 4h per day (outside of office hours) or days at the weekend.

EXPERIENCE

7/2021 - 5/2022 full-time remote Jr. React Native Developer

VStation App Project (https://vsports.app.link/)

Work as part of the development team (10 - 12 people) to develop features for mobile app.

Work with modern tools including Trello, Figma, Gitlab, etc.

Performed unit tests as part of daily work.

React Native / Teamwork / Problem Solving

12/2020 - 6/2021 part-time

Fresher ReactJS Developer

VStation Web Project (https://vsports.com.vn/)

Build some admin features included user, league, team, media page management.

Enhanced the experience for UI/UX design for management, coding skills.

Improve soft skills like communicating with co-workers, problem-solving as well as time manage-

ment.

ReactJS / NextJS / HTML / CSS / Time Management / Teamwork

ACTIVITIES

May 2021 Webhackathon 2021

VNUHCMUIT - WebDev Studios (http://webdevstudios.org/)

Work as a Full-Stack Dev of the team (4 people) to develop a solutions for online learning during the

covid pandemic.

NextJS / NodeJS / Teamwork / Problem Solving

2021 Review Knowledge For The Final Test

HoChiMinh Communist Youth Union of the Class 19CTT4

Prepare slides, documents to help classmate review the knowledge to get the better result in the

final test.

More than 50 students participated

Communication / Summarization / Teamwork

EXTRA SKILLS

Development

Basic Back-End Development

NodeJS / RESTful API / MongoBD / MySQL / Redis / SocketIO

Patterns & Practices

Object-Oriented Programming / Functional Programming

Source Version Control

Git / Gitlab

Foundation Foundation

Programing Languages / OS / DSA / AI / NLP / Computer Networking

EDUCATION

2019 - 2023

Bachelor of Computer Science (Current GPA: 8.3)

VNUHCM - University of Science

Learn the computer science foundation knowledge such as programing languages, data structure and algorithm, AI, natural language processing, operating system, etc...

LANGUAGES

HONORS & AWARDS

Vietnamese - Native English - Upper Intermediate **2nd Place Winner** - Webhackathon 2021 Issued by VNUHCMUIT - WebDev Studios · May 2021